Finding Aid for the Ray Bolger Papers LSC.1117
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 16. Business, Legal, and Financial Records, no dates, ca. 1930s-1980s; Boxes 57, 74-80, 110, 119
  - Contracts, 1940s (Box 57, Folder 12)
    Includes: RKO Radio Pictures, Decca Records, Radio City Music Hall, Roxy Theater.
  - Contracts, 1950s (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Includes: B&R Enterprises, Hotel Sahara, Riviera Hotel, Cocoanut Grove, CBS, NBC.
  - Contracts, ca. 1970s (Box 77, Folder 2)
    Including: CBS, Jack Morton Productions, MCA Records, KNBC, Screen Actor's Guild, and All State Productions.
  - Contracts, ca. 1980s (Box 77, Folder 5)
    Including: Caedmon.
  - Correspondence regarding Nancy Hamilton and Shoe Salesman, 1953 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Dinah's Place - contracts, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - Dividends - holographic notes, 1958-1969 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Financial documents, no date (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Financial documents, ca. 1920s-1930s (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Financial documents, ca. 1940s (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Financial documents, ca. 1950s (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Financial documents, ca. 1960s (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Financial documents, ca. 1970s (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Financial documents, ca. 1980s (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Flamingo, Las Vegas - contract, 1962 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - George White vs. Balban and Katz subpoena, 1932 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Land of Oz - correspondence and clippings, 1969-1970 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Land of Oz - correspondence, clippings, and ephemera, 1970-1971 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Loews contract (Metro) - photo static copy, May 1944 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - McHale's Navy Joins the Airforce - financial statements, 1975, ca. 1980s (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Merv Griffin Show (The) - contract, 1968 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Old Contracts (folder 1 of 2), 1966-1969 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Old Contracts (folder 2 of 2), 1966-1969 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Overseas TV Reports Inc. - contract, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Perry Como Show - contract, 1958 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Pocket planner - Morton bookings and club dates, 1975 (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Real estate property research, 1964 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - RIBO Enterprises, Inc. - minutes and By-laws, 1958-1969 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - RIBO Enterprises, Inc. stock certificates, no date (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Safeway spot - contract, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Screen Actors Guild - agreements and contract, 1962 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Territory of Hawaii court summons regarding Gwen Bolger and Rickard family, 1952 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Tonight Show - contracts, 1968 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Transcontinent Television Corporation Annual Report to Shareholders, 1960 (Box 125, Folder 18)
  - Villa Vista - escrow instructions, correspondence, and clippings, 1969-1970 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Villa Vista - letters of request, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Wizard of Oz (The) - photocopy of contract, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Wizard of Oz (The) - recording contract, Jan 1957 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Wizard of Oz (The) - Scarecrow costume donation to Smithsonian, 1987 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Yeoman Major - contract, 1964 (Box 76, Folder 5)
- Series 17. Music, no dates, ca. 1920s-1980s; Boxes 50, 54-58, 60-65, 67-69, 70-72, 74, 79, 87-100, 102-103, 112, 129- 135
  The Music series consists of printed music sheets, songbooks, commercial sheet music, orchestral parts, vocal parts, and handwritten music sheets. Included is music representing All American, Babes in Toyland, Come Summer, On Your Toes, Sunny, Washington Square, and Wheres Charley?, among others; some items are untitled. Additionally, there are orchestral parts and arrangements which may represent the television program, The Ray Bolger Show. The series is arranged alphabetically by song title.
  - All American - conductor's score, no date (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - All American - piano and vocal arrangements, no date (Box 58)
  - All American - sheet music, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Amy - orchestral parts, no date (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Amy - orchestral parts, no date (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Amy [plus] Encore - orchestral parts, no date (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Amy Bows #2 - conductor's manuscript music sheets, no date (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Amy Bows Slow - orchestral parts, no date (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Amy E flat with Encore - orchestral parts and conductor's score, no date (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Amy Entrance [and] Amy Encore - orchestral parts and manuscript music, no date (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Amy Old Copy - orchestral parts and conductor's score, no date (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Amy Opening extra orch. - orchestral parts, no date (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Amy Original Score - photocopied manuscript music, no date (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Amy without encore - orchestral parts, no date (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - April in Paris - music and lyrics, no date, 1951 (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - April in Paris - sheet music, 1952, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Babes in Toyland - vocal lead sheets and lyrics, no date (Box 70)
  - Begin the Beguine - manuscript music score, no date (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Bolger Opener, Russ Black, Lake Tahoe - orchestral parts and manuscript music, no date (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Bolger Opening - manuscript music, no date (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - Bolger's Sound of Music - conductor's score, 1961 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    Performed for Bohemian Club.
  - Bowl of Cherries - orchestral parts, no date (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - By Jupiter - sheet music, 1942 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Can't Stop Horsin' Around - vocal and instrumental arrangements, no date (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Churkendoose Song, Aw C'mon - manuscript music, no date (Box 99, Folder 6)
    With additional songs for The Boy with the Bonny Bagpipe and the Girl with the Glockenspiel.
  - Come Summer - sheet music, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Commercial sheet music, 1910s-1950s (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Commercial sheet music, 1910s-1950s (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Cut Version of Old Soft Shoe - orchestral parts and manuscript music, no date (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Dance Series - orchestral parts, no date (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Dance Series New '60 - orchestral parts, no date (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Dances Thru the Ages - orchestral parts, no date (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Decca Records - sheet music, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Entertainer (The) - sheet music, no date (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Everything I've Got - orchestral parts and manuscript music (folder 1 of 2), no date (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Everything I've Got - orchestral parts and manuscript music (folder 2 of 2), no date (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Fillers, no date (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - First Dance - orchestral parts and conductor's score, no date (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Four Jacks and a Jill - sheet music, 1941 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - George White's Scandals - sheet music, 1924 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Getting Married - manuscript music, no date (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Girl Named Amy (A) - orchestral parts, no date (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Happy Face - orchestral parts, no date (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Happy Face - orchestral parts, no date (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Happy Time (The) - score, 1967-1968 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Happy Time (The) - score, 1967-1968 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Harvey Girls (The) - sheet music, 1945 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Heller - orchestral score, no date (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - I'd Have Baked a Cake lyrics, no date (Box 74, Folder 1)
    With It's So Nice to Have a Man Around the House sheet music.
  - If You Knew Susie - orchestral parts and conductor's score, no date (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Judy Garland Show (The) - sheet music, no date (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Keep Off the Grass - sheet music, no date (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Last Dance - orchestral parts and conductor's score, no date (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Let's Take a Walk and Let a Smile Be Your Umbrella - orchestral parts, no date (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Life Is Just a Bowl of Cherries - orchestral parts and conductor's score, no date (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Look for the Silver Lining - conductor's score pages, no date (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Lyrics for unidentified projects, no date, 1953 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Lyrics submitted to Bolger from Alan Greene, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript music pages, no date (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript music scores, no date (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript music scores, no date (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript music scores, no date (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Married in the Morning - orchestral parts, no date (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Music of Sound - orchestral parts, no date (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Old Soft Shoe - orchestral parts, no date (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Old Soft Shoe - orchestral parts, no date (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - Old Soft Shoe - orchestral parts and conductor's score, no date (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Old Soft Shoe - orchestral parts and conductor's score, no date (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Old Soft Shoe - photocopied manuscript score (folder 1 of 2), no date (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Old Soft Shoe - photocopied manuscript score (folder 2 of 2), no date (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Old Soft Shoe [plus] extra violin parts in different key "B" - orchestral parts, no date (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Old Soft Shoe Ford Show - orchestral parts, no date (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Old Soft Shoes - orchestral parts, no date (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - On Your Toes - sheet music, 1936 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Once in Love with Amy - vocal and orchestral parts, no date (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Orchestral parts - master copies, no date (Box 134, Folder 1)
    Bolger Opening, Dearie, The Look of Love, Sunnyside.
  - Orchestral parts - master copies, no date (Box 134, Folder 2)
    Dance Series, Pretty Girl Strip.
  - Orchestral parts - master copies, no date (Box 134, Folder 3)
    Bolger Overture, Entre'Act.
  - Orchestral parts - master copies, no date (Box 134, Folder 4)
    Amy.
  - Orchestral parts - master copies, no date (Box 134, Folder 5)
    Amy, Girl Named Amy.
  - Orchestral parts - master copies A - W, no date (Box 133)
  - Orchestral parts - master copies W - Y, no date (Box 134)
  - Orchestral parts A - O, no date (Box 129)
  - Orchestral parts O - W, no date (Box 130)
  - Orchestrations (A-C), no date, 1959 (Box 64)
  - Orchestrations (C-L), no date (Box 65)
    With Life is Like a Bowl Full of Cherries.
  - Orchestrations (S-T), no date, 1936 (Box 66)
    With Sad Sack.
  - Orchestrations (W-Y), no date (Box 67)
    With Washington Square.
  - Photocopies of song titles 1870s-1970s, no date (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Photostats of vocal piano number Weekend Cruise, 1956 (Box 131, Folder 6)
    With other commercial sheet music.
  - Pretty Girl Like A Melody (A) - conductor's score and sheet music, no date (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Prize Fight Number - orchestral parts, no date (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Ray Bolger Show (The) - Orchestrations, no date (Box 58)
    Appears to be for The Ray Bolger Show.
  - Ray Bolger Show (The) - Orchestrations, no date (Box 59)
    Appears to be for The Ray Bolger Show episodes 5A, 6A, and 10A.
  - Ray Bolger Show (The) - Orchestrations, no date (Box 60)
    Appears to be for The Ray Bolger Show episodes 11A-13A.
  - Ray Bolger Show (The) - Orchestrations, no date (Box 61)
    Appears to be for The Ray Bolger Show episodes 14A.
  - Ray Bolger Show (The) - Orchestrations, no date (Box 62)
    Appears to be for The Ray Bolger Show episodes 15A-16A.
  - Ray Bolger Show (The) - Orchestrations, no date (Box 63)
    Appears to be for The Ray Bolger Show episodes 26A and 30A.
  - Ray Bolger Show (The) - Orchestrations, no date (Box 87)
    Appears to be for The Ray Bolger Show episodes 2A-3A, 8A-9A.
  - Ray Bolger Show (The) - Orchestrations, no date (Box 88)
    Appears to be for The Ray Bolger Show episodes 10A-11A.
  - Ray Bolger Show (The) - Orchestrations, no date (Box 89)
    Appears to be for The Ray Bolger Show episodes 12A, 14A, 17A.
  - Ray Bolger Show (The) - Orchestrations, no date (Box 90)
    Appears to be for The Ray Bolger Show episodes 17A-18A.
  - Ray Bolger Show (The) - Orchestrations, no date (Box 91)
    Appears to be for The Ray Bolger Show episodes 19A-20A, 29A.
  - Ray Bolger Show (The) - Orchestrations, no date (Box 92)
    Appears to be for The Ray Bolger Show episodes 20A-21A.
  - Ray Bolger Show (The) - Orchestrations, no date (Box 93)
    Appears to be for The Ray Bolger Show episodes 28A-29A.
  - Ray Bolger Show (The) - Orchestrations, no date (Box 94)
  - Ray Bolger Show (The) - Orchestrations, no date (Box 69)
  - Riddler (The) - photocopied manuscript music pages, no date (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Sad Sack - orchestral parts, no date (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Sad Sack extra parts - orchestral parts, no date (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Sad Sack Ford Show - orchestral parts, no date (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Shake, Rattle, and Roll - manuscript music, no date (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Sheet music with lyrics written by Gwen and Ray Bolger, no date (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Show Opener - orchestral parts, no date (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Songbooks (A-J), ca. 1920s-1980s (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Songbooks (M-Z), ca. 1920s-1980s (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Sound of Music - orchestral parts, no date (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Sound of Music as at Colorado Springs - orchestral parts, no date (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Spring Fever - orchestral parts and conductor's score, no date (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Stage Door Canteen - manuscript music pages, no date (Box 122)
  - Sunny - sheet music, 1925 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Sweet Georgia Brown orchestral parts, no date (Box 63)
  - Tangos: La Comparsita/Derecho Viejo - orchestral parts, no date (Box 101, Folder 8)
    Possibly music for Where's Raymond?.
  - Tea for Two - orchestral parts, no date (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - They All Left A Little On the Floor - conductor's score, no date (Box 122)
  - They All Left a Little on the Floor - music manuscript and lyrics, no date (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - They All Left a Little on the Floor - orchestral part, no date (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - They All Left a Little on the Floor - orchestral parts, no date (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - They All Left a Little on the Floor - orchestral parts, no date (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - They All Left a Little on the Floor - orchestral parts (folder 1 of 2), no date (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - They All Left a Little on the Floor - orchestral parts (folder 2 of 2), no date (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Think Mink - orchestral parts, no date (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Think Mink - orchestral parts, no date (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Think Mink Finale - orchestral parts, no date (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Three to Make Ready - sheet music, 1946 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Tunetown - sheet music and manuscript music, 1970 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Unidentified music sheets, no date (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Various orchestral and vocal parts (A-S), no date, 1927, 1945, 1959-1960, 1981 (Box 68)
  - Various orchestral and vocal parts (T-Y), no date, 1929, 1946 (Box 69)
    With small amount of manuscript music sheets.
  - Various orchestral parts, no date (Box 70)
  - Various orchestral parts (A-S), no date (Box 102, Folder 7)
    Including: Amy, Fascinating, Life is Just a Bowl of Cherries, Old Soft Shoe, and Sound of Music.
  - Various orchestral parts (T-W), no date (Box 102, Folder 8)
    Including: They All Left a Little on the Floor and Wizard of Oz.
  - Various orchestral parts and music scores (I-S), no date, 1915, 1958 (Box 71)
    With Once in Love with Amy.
  - Various orchestral parts and music scores (W), no date (Box 72)
  - Various vocal and orchestral parts, no date (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Various vocal parts, no date (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Washington Square - sheet music, no date, 1956 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - What Makes a Star - arrangement, no date (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - What Makes a Star - manuscript music score, no date (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - What Makes a Star - orchestral parts, no date (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - What Makes a Star - orchestral parts, no date (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Where's Charley - score, no date (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Where's Charley? - sheet music, 1948 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Who Gives a Sou - vocal parts, no date (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Who's Where in Music rate and date information, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Wizard of Oz Brain insert (old copy) - orchestral parts, no date (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - You Make Me Feel So Young - orchestral parts, no date (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Young Anymore - orchestral parts, no date (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Ziegfeld Follies - sheet music, 1931 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Commercial Sheet Music
    - Alabamy Bound, 1954 (Box 57)
      Scope and Content
      Music: Ray Henderson Lyrics: B.G. De Sylva, Bud Green
    - Alone, 1935 (Box 130)
      Music: Nacio Herb Brown Lyric: Arthur Freed
      From the motion picture A Night at the Opera
    - All Right, All Right, All Right, 1936 (Box 130)
      Music: Rudy Vallee (photograph on cover) Lyrics: Rudy Vallee, Dave Franklin
      On cover: photograph of Major Edward Bowes
    - Always and Always, 1937 (Box 130)
      Music: Edward Ward Lyric: Bob Wright, Chet Forrest
      From the motion picture, Mannequin
      On cover: photograph of Joan Crawford
    - Another Perfect Night is Ending, 1936 (Box 130)
      Music: J. Fred Coots Words: Benny Davis
      On cover: photograph of Henry Busse
    - Are You From Dixie (Caus I'm From Dixie Too), 1915 (Box 57)
      Music: George L. Cobb Words: Jack Yellen
    - At Sundown (Love is Calling Me Home), 1927 (Box 130)
      Composer: Walter Donaldson
    - Babes in the Woods, 1964 (Box 57)
      From the musical of the same title. Composer: Rick Besoyan
    - Be a Good Sport, 1937 (Box 130)
      Composers: Mack Gordon, Harry Revel
      From the motion picture, Love and Hisses
    - Between the Devil and the Deep Blue Sea, 1931 (Box 57)
      From Rhythm Mania Music: Harold Arlen Lyrics: Ted Koehler
    - Broadway's Gone Hawaii, 1937 (Box 130)
      Composers: Harry Reve, Mack Gordon
    - Brush Up Your Shakespeare, 1949 (Box 57)
      From: Kiss Me Kate Composer: Cole Porter
    - But Where Are You, 1936 (Box 57)
      From the RKO motion picture Follow the Fleet Composer: Irving Berlin
    - Cafe Continental, 1936 (Box 130)
      Composers: Jimmy Kennedy, Will Grosz
      On cover: photograph of Guy Lombardo
    - Call Me Darling (Box 130)
    - Can't You See, 1965 (Box 57)
      From the musical Golden Boy Music: Charles Strouse Lyric: Lee Adams
    - Chinese Lullaby, 1919 (Box 57)
      From the motion picture East is West.
      Photograph of Lupe Velez on cover. Composer: Robert Hood Bowers
    - Close to You, 1936 (Box 130)
      Music: L. Raymond Smith Words: Joe Young
      On cover: photograph of Joe Reichman
    - Come Out, Come Out, Wherever You Are, 1944 (Box 57)
      From the motion picture Step Lively
      Music: Jule Styne Lyric: Sammy Cahn
      Photograph of Frank Sinatra on cover
    - Cuban Love Song, 1931 (Box 57)
      Composers: Herbert Stothart, Jimmy McHugh, Dorothy Fields
      From the motion picture of the same title. On cover: photograph of Lawrence Tibbett
    - Cucaracha, La (Box 130)
    - Cupid's Dance, 1901 (Box 57)
      Composer: Emil Hahn
    - Dancing in the Dark, 1931 (Box 57)
      From: The Band Wagon On cover: photographs of Fred and Adele Astaire, Helen Broderick, Frank Morgan, Tilly Losch
      Composer: Arthur Schwartz
    - Danny Boy, 1913 (Box 130)
      Compoer: Fred. E. Weatherly
    - Dark Eyes = Otchi Tchorniya, 1929 (Box 130)
      English lyrics: joseph Kammen Piano arrangement, Jack Kammen
    - Daughter of Rosie O'Grady, 1918 (Box 57)
      Music: Walter Donaldson Words: Monty C. Brice
    - Ding Dong the Witch is Dead, 1939 (Box 131)
      Music: Harold Arlen Lyrics: E.Y. Harburg
      From the motion picture The Wizard of Oz.
    - Donkey Serenade, 1937 (Box 130)
      From the motion picture, The Firefly
      On cover: photographs of Jeannette Macdonald, Allan Jones.
      Composers: Rudolf Friml, Herbert Stothart
    - Don't Blame Me, 1923 (Box 57)
      From the motion picture, Big Cit.
      Music: Jimmy McHugh Lyric: Dorothy Fields
    - Don't Take Your Love From Me, 1941 (Box 130)
      Composer: Henry Nemo On cover: photograph of Joan Brooks
    - Dream a Little Dream of Me, 1931 (Box 130)
      Music: W. Schwandet, F. Andree Words: Gus Kahn
      On cover: photograph of Bill Hogan
    - Dream, Dream, Dream, 1954 (Box 57)
      Music: Jimmy McHugh Lyrics: Mitchell Parish
    - Dream Time, 1936 (Box 130)
      On cover photograph of Carl Ravazza
    - Ev'ry Day Away From You, 1929 (Box 57)
      Music: Jay Mills Lyric: Charles Tobias
    - Ev'rything I've Got, 1942 (Box 57)
      Music: Richard Rodgers Words: Lorenz Hart
    - Everything Stops For Tea, 1935 (Box 130)
      Composers: Maurice Sigler, Al Goodhart, Al Hoffman
    - Everything You Said Came True, 1937 (Box 130)
      Composers: Cliff Friend, Dave Franklin ' On cover: photograph of Ray Heatherton
    - Exactly Like You, 1930 (Box 57)
    - Five Minutes More, 1946 (Box 57)
    - Flying Down to Rio, 1933 (Box 130)
      Music: Vincent Youmans Words: Gus Kahn, Edward Eliscu
      From the motion picture of the same title
      On cover: photograph of Fred Astaire, Ginger Rogers
    - Fun to Be Fooled, 1934 (Box 131)
      Music: Harold Arlen Words: Ira Gershwin, E.Y. Harburg From the musical revue, Life Begins at 8:40
    - Girl Friend (Lennie and Mollie), 1926 (Box 57)
    - Glory of Love, 1936 (Box 130)
      Composer: Billy Hill
      On cover: photograph of Bing Crosby
    - God Touched the Rose, 1921 (Box 130)
      Music: Mary Helen Brown Words: Iona Le Brun
    - Gone (Box 130)
      From the motion picture, Love on the Run
    - Goodbye, Old Girl, 1955 (Box 57)
      From the Broadway production, Damn Yankees Composers: Richard Adler, Jerry Ross
    - Goody Goody, 1936 (Box 130)
      Composers: Johnny Mercer, Matt Malneck
      On cover, photograph of Kate Smith
    - Goopy Geer (He Plays Piano, and He Plays By Ear), 1931 (Box 130)
      Composer: Herman Hupfeld
    - Got to Dance My Way to Heaven, 1936 (Box 130)
      Composer: Sam Coslow
      From the motion picture, It's Love Again.
      On cover: photograph of Jessie Matthews
    - Hallelujah, 1927 (Box 130)
      Music: Vincent Youmans Words: Leo Robin, Clifford Grey From the motion picture, Hit the Deck
      On cover: photograph of Jack Oakie, Polly Walker
    - Happiness is a Thing Called Joe, 1942 (Box 57)
      Music: Harold Arlen Lyric: E.Y. Harburg
      From the motion picture, Cabin in the Sky
    - Happy Glow, 1952 (Box 57)
      Music: Emil Stern, Eddie Barclay Lyrics: James Crawford
    - Harbor Lights, 1937 (Box 57)
      Composers: Jimmy Kennedy, Hugh Williams
    - Heigh Ho, 1938 (Box 130)
      Music: Frank Churchill Words: Larry Morey
      From the motion picture, Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs
    - Helena, 1964 (Box 57)
      From the musical Babes in the Wood. Composer: Rick Besoyan
    - Here's to Romance, 1935 (Box 130)
      Composers: Con Conrad, Herb Magidson
      On cover: photograph of Nino Martini
    - Hey! Young Fella (Close Your Old Umbrella), 1933 (Box 57)
    - Home on the Range, 1930 (Box 130)
      Arranger: David W. Guion
    - Homecoming, 1976 (Box 57)
      Composer: Hagood Hardy Arranger, Russ Taylor
    - I Can't Believe That You're in Love With Me, 1926 (Box 57)
      Composers: Clarence Gaskill, Jimmy McHugh.
      From the motion picture, The Caine Mutiny.
      On cover: photographs of Humphrey Bogart, Jose Ferrer, Van Johnson, Fred MacMurray
    - I Feel a Song Comin' On, 1935 (Box 57)
      Composers: Jimmy McHugh, Dorothy Fields, George Oppenheimer
    - I Feel Like a Feather in the Breeze, 1935 (Box 57)
      From the motion picture, Collegiate Composers: Mack Gordon, Harry Revel On cover: photographs of Joe Penner, Jack Oakie, Ned Sparks, Frances Langford
    - I Got Plenty o' Nuttin', 1935 (Box 130)